Privacy Policy                                                                               

### Owner

SPECTRUM INPUT LLC DBA PreciseFP  
1766 Wilshire Blvd,  
Los Angeles, CA 90025,

**Owner contact email:** info@precisefp.com

### Introduction

Spectrum Input, LLC, the developer of PreciseFP, a client data-gathering tool used by financial professionals, is committed to protecting your privacy by ensuring the security of your information on our website.

Spectrum Input, LLC will never disclose or share your personally identifiable information with a third party that is not a sub-processor associated with Spectrum Input LLC, unless required by law to do so (for example, to comply with a subpoena).

If you were invited to use PreciseFP by a financial professional, you should also verify his/her Privacy Policy. Your financial advisor and, if applicable, the firm with whom he/she is licensed, also has access to your personal information on PreciseFP. Your advisor uses your personal information, in conjunction with our software, to provide customized financial planning services. Your advisor’s use of your data is governed by their firm’s Privacy Policy. Please contact your financial advisor if you have questions about his/her firm’s Privacy Policy.

### What Personal Information Do We Collect and How Do We Use It?

When you register for the first time, we will ask you to provide pieces of information that help us locate you within our system. Examples are your name, e-mail address, and contact information. You will also be asked to create a password, which should not be shared with anyone.

We use your name to personalize your financial professional’s unique PreciseFP online client forms and PDFs; both of which are generated by the system. We use your email address to confirm your subscription, username and password, and to provide customer service. As a registered user, when you select the option to customize, create or access your client forms, we will recognize you by your username and password. We may also use the contact information we collect to notify you about any new functions included in our software or new services offered by our website.

We share some of your personal information with vendors/sub-processors with the purpose of providing an essential service to Spectrum Input, LLC. An audited minimum relevant set of personal information is shared with each vendor. Here is a list of our vendors that process personal information:

1. **AWS (Amazon Web Services)** – The bulk of your data will be stored in our infrastructure hosted with AWS.
2. **Stripe** – Payment / subscription information is stored and managed here.
3. **Intercom** – Support and marketing platform that provides our online chat messenger and automated emails.
4. **Bugsnag** – Alert platform used for identifying and debugging errors.
5. **Google** – Analytical data is stored and processed here through products like Analytics, or Drive.

What Financial Information Do We Collect and How Do We Use It?
--------------------------------------------------------------

To use our online client forms, your financial professional will invite you to input personal financial data for you and, if applicable, your spouse or partner, and any other family members that you identify. The requested personal financial data can include, but is not limited to, such components as annual income, current values of and annual additions to investment assets, and lifetime and legacy-related goals. In many instances, these entries are optional. All financial professionals’ forms are unique, since PreciseFP allows for the editing of form templates. Fields and other content within the forms will vary from one account to another. Our software facilitates the capturing, storage, and transmission of data that relates specifically to you and your unique financial situation.

### Cookies

“Cookies” are small files used by web sites to store information on your computer. For PreciseFP to work properly, your browser must be enabled to accept cookies. Our cookies contain information that identifies you during a session and allows the software to function. This information is used only by PreciseFP and is not for sale or distribution.

### How Do We Protect Your Information?

When you access your financial data, we use a state-of-the-art secure server environment to keep all of your personal information as secure as possible. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us, and all data we collect is protected against unauthorized access. This approach helps ensure that your personal and financial information remains safe and private.

### Your Consent

By using the Application, you consent to the collection and use of the information described above by Spectrum Input, LLC.

You also acknowledge that Spectrum Input, LLC can use aggregated data from its users and subscribers to better understand our user base and/or to research potential changes in content and services. Spectrum Input, LLC may use this collective information for product research or marketing demographics, but any such information will never be disclosed, sold, or distributed to a third party where such information could ever indicate directly or indirectly any individual’s financial information.

### Your Rights

You have the right, at any time, to contact us to and verify the accuracy of your personal information or to ask for it to be supplemented, cancelled, updated or corrected, or to block any data held in violation of the law, as well as to oppose their treatment for any legitimate reason. Requests should be sent to the contact information set out above.

This Application does not support “Do Not Track” requests.

### Changes to this privacy policy

We reserve the right to make changes to this privacy policy at any time by giving notice to its Users on this page. If a User objects to any of the changes to the Policy, the User must cease using this Application and can request the removal of all their Personal Data. Unless stated otherwise, the then-current privacy policy applies to all stored Personal Data.

### Legal information

Notice to European Users: this privacy statement has been prepared in fulfillment of the obligations under Art. 10 of EC Directive n. 95/46/EC, and under the provisions of Directive 2002/58/EC, as revised by Directive 2009/136/EC, on the subject of Cookies.

_May 24th, 2018_

#### About Us

#### Product

#### Resources

© 2024 Docupace Technologies  

Manage Consent

To provide the best experiences, we use technologies like cookies to store and/or access device information. Consenting to these technologies will allow us to process data such as browsing behavior or unique IDs on this site. Not consenting or withdrawing consent, may adversely affect certain features and functions.

Functional  Functional Always active

The technical storage or access is strictly necessary for the legitimate purpose of enabling the use of a specific service explicitly requested by the subscriber or user, or for the sole purpose of carrying out the transmission of a communication over an electronic communications network.

Preferences  Preferences

The technical storage or access is necessary for the legitimate purpose of storing preferences that are not requested by the subscriber or user.

Statistics  Statistics

The technical storage or access that is used exclusively for statistical purposes. The technical storage or access that is used exclusively for anonymous statistical purposes. Without a subpoena, voluntary compliance on the part of your Internet Service Provider, or additional records from a third party, information stored or retrieved for this purpose alone cannot usually be used to identify you.

Marketing  Marketing

The technical storage or access is required to create user profiles to send advertising, or to track the user on a website or across several websites for similar marketing purposes.

Accept Deny View preferences Save preferences [View preferences](#)

Manage consent

#### THE PRECISEFP BLOG

Ideas You Can Use
=================

Stay updated with the latest insights, tips, and best practices for financial advisors on the PreciseFP blog.

##### [Tech Talk: Better Client Experiences Start Here](https://precisefp.com/blog/tech-talk-better-client-experiences-start-here/)

##### [Take Back Your Time: PreciseFP Integrations to Consider](https://precisefp.com/blog/take-back-your-time-precisefp-integrations-to-consider/)

##### [How to Find the Perfect Client for Your Firm](https://precisefp.com/blog/how-to-find-the-perfect-client-for-your-firm/)

### Make Sure Your Client Forms are Pixel Perfect

Explore the industry-wide shift that did away with big stacks of paperwork and the role PreciseFP has played in facilitating e-signature capabilities nationwide.
